Hey, come on, man.
We have to go work
on our science project.
I am doing science.
Look, centrifugal force.
Moseby, Nina
fryburger just threw
the most incredible
birthday party for a dog.
Ivana's upset.
Of course she is.
Look at that stupid
hat you put on her.
Cat person.
So, now I want a bigger,
better party for Ivana
in the grand ballroom.
Here's the guest list.
I will take care
of it personally.
Thank you. Mm-hmm.
Maddie, take care
of it personally.
No one else will touch it?
Not with a 10-foot
pooper-scooper.
Oh, Mr. Moseby,
you receive a fax.
The Tipton hotel inspector
is on the way for
surprise inspection.
But how can it be a
surprise inspection
if they sent a fax?
Because the fax came 2 weeks ago
and I forgot to give it to you.
Surprise!
Fortunately for all of us,
my hotel is always
in tiptop Tipton shape,
and nothing has changed
since the last inspection.
Except for that.
♪ Here I am in your life ♪
♪ here you are in mine ♪
♪ yes, we have a Suite Life ♪
♪ most of the time ♪
♪ you and
me got the world to see ♪
♪ so come on down ♪
♪ just me
and you know what to do ♪
♪ so come on down ♪
♪ it's you
and me and me and you ♪
♪ we got the
whole place to ourselves ♪
♪ you and
me, we got it all for free ♪
♪ so come on down ♪
♪ this is the Suite Life ♪
♪ we've got a Suite Life ♪
hey, Muriel, when
you were cleaning in there,
did you see a $5.00 bill?
I thought you
were throwing that away.
It was on my dresser.
My bad.
Hide me!
Whoa, whoa, whoa. What happened?
Mr. Moseby's after me
just 'cause I
was playing yo-yo in the lobby,
and it might
have landed in his mug.
And then?
I ran after that.
He scares me.
Mr. Moseby's just doing his job.
He needs to keep
this hotel running smoothly,
and you tend to be unsmooth.
Yeah, unsmooth
like when mom doesn't shave
her legs for 2 weeks.
Aren't you two
supposed to be working
on your science experiment?
We've already started. Look!
Aah! No, no, no, no!
What... what
are you doing with those rats?
Science.
We got them from our school.
This is
Bonnie, and that's Clyde.
They're our experiment.
Which is what?
Giving your
mother a heart attack?
No, actually,
rap music for Bonnie
and heavy metal for Clyde,
and then Cody writes down
a whole
bunch of scientific stuff.
You know, behavioral
changes, like eating habits,
mood swings, urination patterns.
Eww!
Why does it have to be rats?!
Too late now. We've bonded.
Swell.
Well, if you don't mind,
I'm going to take
Bonnie and Clyde away
from where we eat.
I'll get it.
No. Wait. What
if it's Mr. Moseby?
I'm toast.
Come in.
Look, Mr. Moseby, if this is
about the yo-yo, then I'm...
Oh, pish posh.
Boys will be boys. You
were just having fun,
and that's what
boys do, isn't it?
They have fun. Ha ha ha!
Did that yo-yo
bounce off your head?
No. I'm fine.
I came up here to
offer you scamps
tickets to today's Red Sox game.
It's a matinee.
The sox game? All right!
And your seats are
just above that little hut
wherein the players spit
and scratch themselves.
Hold on.
There's something wrong here.
Why do you question
my generosity?
Yeah. Why do you
question his generosity?
I'll tell you what. You go.
I think I'll just stay
here and hang out
in the old lobby.
Where's my model rocket? Oh.
No!
All right, fine.
The hotel inspector
will be arriving soon,
and it would be marvelous
if you weren't around.
I knew it!
We'll be not around longer
if you throw in a
little money for dinner.
I like lobster.
Uh-huh. Ok, fine.
What are you doing?
I'm taking Clyde to the game.
You can't do that!
It'll contaminate
the experiment.
Who knows what take
me out to the ballgame
will do to his urinary pattern?
Fine, but this is why
they like me more
than they like you.
Come on, guys!
If we make batting practice,
I might meet a player!
Ok, I'll take you,
but don't tell Cody.
Oh, sorry, Bonnie.
I didn't know you'd
want to go, too.
How sexist of me.
When is the hotel
inspector going to be here?
Zack and Cody are
gonna be back any minute.
Oh, don't worry, Mr. Moseby.
Per your instructions, I
am gluing down the vase.
Soon it'll be twinproof.
I have the most fantastic
idea for Ivana's party.
Canceling it?
Don't be silly.
I saw this fabulous painting
of dogs playing poker.
Ivana wants a poker party.
You do know those dogs
weren't really playing poker?
If they weren't playing poker,
how did that dalmatian
win all the money, huh?
Poker party it is.
Oh, yes!
Ohh!
Thank you, Esteban.
You can let go now.
I wish I could.
They don't call it
mega-glue for nothing.
Mr. Moseby?
That's right. May I help you?
I am Ilsa shikelgrubermiger,
the Tipton hotel inspector.
Yes, of course.
We were expecting you hours ago.
I got held up at Logan airport.
Traffic?
No. Their whole
luggage system stinks.
I had to redo it.
Welcome to the Tipton.
Mr. Moseby, do you realize
you are wearing a bellhop?
Very droll.
It goes with your
devastating good looks.
Are you staring at
my beauty Mark?
Yes. No.
Oh, would you stop that?
Yes, sir! Ow!
Let go!
If I could just... let me...
Ooh, I love the
vest look on you, sir.
But like your sleeves, I am off.
Might I explain?
Hey, Mr. Moseby.
The sox won 10 to 9.
And mom caught a foul ball.
Yeah, apparently heads
up means heads down.
So is the evil hotel
inspector gone yet?
No. She's right here.
Whoa! What's that on your face?
It's a beauty Mark.
But it has a hair
on it. I mean...
It's a good thing I
don't have triplets.
I've run out of hands.
Thanks again for the
tickets to the game.
Yeah, thanks.
We know they're
usually for the guests,
so we really appreciate it.
Oh, ignores guest
needs for friends.
They're not my friends. Oh.
Ignores guest
needs for strangers.
Ugh!
What kind of hotel
manager are you?
He's the best. He's number one.
Yeah, last week, he let us
cook s'mores in the kitchen,
and then he put out
the fire all by himself.
Ok!
Mr. Moseby, I have
been here 5 minutes,
and I am not impressed.
I assure you, there will
be no more surprises.
Aah! Rats!
Starting now.
Mr. Moseby, in my 20
years as a hotel inspector,
I have never been so appalled.
Rats in the lobby? Yeah, but...
Dut, dut, dut!
I am taking over the
management of this hotel
until a review board arrives
to make their final decision.
Your Tipton hotel keys.
Not his keys.
Your gold-plated Tipton badge.
Not the badge!
Your Tipton tie.
I feel compelled to disclose
that I am wearing custom-made
Tipton boxer shorts.
Dry-clean them
and send them back.
Oh, poor Mr. Moseby.
Yeah.
But what are the odds
there are 2 rats downstairs
and we have 2 rats upstairs?
They are upstairs, aren't they?
Well... oh!
I mean, they were in my pocket
when we got back from the game.
They must've snuck out
when we got to the hotel.
You ruined our
science experiment.
And more importantly,
you may have ruined Mr. Moseby.
Zack, you better think
about you just did.
You may have
cost the man his job.
Here, Bonnie. Here, Clyde.
It's been a whole week.
I don't think this
cheese is working.
Muriel, what is this?
Mmm! Gorgonzola.
You want some? There's
more under the couch.
Esteban! Yes, sir.
Ma'am.
What is that nonregulation pin
you are wearing on
your Tipton uniform?
It belonged to my
great-grandfather
who died fighting for my
country's independence.
How touching. Take it off.
I'm watching you.
Man, I never thought
I'd miss Moseby.
Yeah, she's a real witch.
I'd love to vacuum
off that mole.
You there, candy girl.
My name's Maddie.
Ja, candy girl.
I see you punched in at 4:01.
You were supposed
to be here at 4:00
to work on London's
poochie party.
Sorry.
4:00 means 4:00.
I am docking you
for that minute.
Th-that's a dime.
A dime you'll never see!
Man, getting
Mr. Moseby suspended
was the worst thing
we've ever done.
And by "we," you mean you?
Now, I'm gonna go
over there and talk to her.
If things don't go well, I
want you to have my yo-yo.
Excuse me, miss
shikel-geiger counter...
Close enough. What?
What are you staring at?
Nothing.
I just wanted to
say that the rat thing
was not Mr. Moseby's fault.
It was my fault.
Well, that changes
things. Really?
No!
A manager is
responsible for everything
that happens in a hotel.
The buck stops here.
Speaking of which,
I want the two of you
to stop coming in the
front entrance Willy-nilly.
But Mr. Moseby always lets us...
Mr. Moseby doesn't
work here anymore.
But we need... dut, dut, dut!
End of conversation.
It's been 31 minutes.
That pizza is free!
Hello, Mr. Moseby.
Zack.
Wow, your apartment is
decorated just like the Tipton lobby.
There was a 2-for-1 sale.
What brings you here?
You gotta come back, Mr. Moseby.
Ilsa's a nightmare.
I'm sorry to hear that,
but there is nothing
that I can do.
I've been suspended.
Now, I hope you
enjoyed your stay
at the Moseby apartment.
You can't give up.
The Tipton is your whole life.
Not necessarily. I
have other interests.
I've always wanted to
learn to drive the big rigs.
Breaker, breaker,
pedal to the metal!
But we need you
back, and I'll promise
I'll never bring a rodent
through the lobby again.
That was you?
Yes, and I'm sorry.
I'm totally, completely,
absolutely sorry,
really, really sorry.
Thank you for coming up
here and telling me that,
but if you'll excuse
me, I am in the middle
of a very important project.
That's the Tipton.
Mm-hmm. 1/100th scale.
Wow, you got the tip just right.
Don't... Touch that.
Sorry?
I don't understand.
I went and apologized
to Mr. Moseby,
but things still
aren't any better.
Well, it's good that
you apologized,
but that doesn't
always fix everything.
That stinks.
That's life.
Sometimes it takes more
than just saying you're sorry.
Try to get some sleep, ok?
Ok.
I love you.
Love you, too.
Bonnie, Clyde, thank
goodness you're back!
Cody, wake up.
Are we moving again?
No, look who came
back. Bonnie and Clyde.
Yes!
Oh, thank goodness we found them
before the dog party.
That would have been a disaster.
Yeah, the kind that'll
get a manager fired.
Cody, it's a brilliant plan!
Thanks.
What's my plan again?
Hello?
Is this the cat lovers society?
Is this the head cat?
Well, you and your entire group
have just won a free
weekend at the Tipton hotel.
Th-that's right.
Bring as many
kitties as you'd like.
Yeah!
Look who's been
assigned to a new room.
Everybody!
Oh, boy.
Dut, dut, dut, dut!
Put a lederhosen in it, Blondie.
Esteban, what is going
on with the computer?
I don't know. Every
time I push a button,
I get a picture of a koala bear.
Ooh, and he's doing a dance!
Look how cute.
Have you tried to restart it?
Only Mr. Moseby knows
how. I've tried everything.
Have you tried this?
Oh, you have broken it.
Ohh!
What is going on out here?
You're disturbing Ivana's party.
They're playing
spin the milk-bone.
I don't have time for your
petty puppy problems.
Grr! Grr!
Ha! You don't scare me.
I once bit a shark.
London, we have a problem.
What are you doing out here?
You're supposed to be making
balloon people for the dogs.
I've had it! 2 of
your guests bit me,
and one went tinkle on my leg!
No! Don't make
me go back in there!
Excuse me.
Excuse me. We're here
for the cat lovers convention.
The what?
We were promised free rooms
and complimentary litter boxes.
Let me check that for you.
I can't seem to find it.
Phase one complete.
Get Moseby here.
Tipton ho... Moseby residence.
Mr. Moseby, it's Zack!
You gotta get over here.
The place is going
crazy, and we need you!
I'm sure Ilsa can handle it.
Oh, no, the water
is up to my neck!
Losing... air... fast.
There's water in my hotel?
Take your sticking paws
off me, you dirty ape!
There are apes in my hotel?
Help! There's an angry mob
running through the lobby!
L-look out!
The Tipton needs
me. I'm coming, mama!
On to phase 3: Release the rats.
Bonnie, Clyde, we've
gone over the plan.
You know what to do.
Remember, we're
doing this for Moseby.
Aah!
For the love of schnitzel.
This may be our best work ever.
Only if it gets Moseby back.
Miss shikelgrubermiger,
I am martino guistefester.
Ambrose lippencollarman,
Bob Smith.
Oh!
From the Tipton review board.
Is there any way
you could come back,
mm, not now?
Get this mangy mutt off of me!
Stop.
Bad dog. No.
Good gracious! What
is going on here?!
Perfect timing.
Dogs, halt!
Wait! Stop! You
forgot your doggy bags!
Sit.
Now go back to your party.
There's nothing to see here.
Ladies and gentlemen,
may I have your
attention, please?
All of your complaints will
be handled immediately.
Ah, Mr. Takimoto.
, mademoiselle Chantal.
Ah, Mr. Moombassa.
Cool.
Esteban!
Yes, your majesty?
I want gift baskets for each
of these guests immediately.
Oh, and some catnip
for our feline friends.
Oh, for you, anything.
And for you, bubkes.
Mr. Moseby, on behalf
of the Tipton review board,
I must say I am very impressed.
Well, thank you, sir.
I'll have you know
I had everything under control.
Not from where we stand.
I think this review is done.
You obviously cannot
inspire loyalty in staff,
and you certainly are
not fit to run a hotel.
This isn't a hotel!
This is a circus with dogs
and cats and rats
and clowns and twins.
The only thing missing
is a bearded lady.
Watch it.
You would have to be out
of your mind to work here.
Well, then call me crazy.
Mr. Moseby, please
continue your fine work.
Ms. Shikelgrubermiger,
your Tipton keys,
your nametag, and your pen.
Aah!
No hard feelings?
Psych!
I'll get you next
time, Mr. Moseby,
and your little dog, too!
Dut, dut, dut!
Was all of this your doing?
It was Zack.
I'm sorry, Mr. Moseby.
So, you engineered this mayhem,
nearly destroying my
hotel in the process?
Yes, I did.
I just have one thing to
say to you, young man.
Thank you.
My pleasure.
Hey, hey, I helped
destroy the hotel, too.
You know, boys, next week,
the health inspector's coming.
You ever been to New York?
Throw in Yankees
tickets, and we're there.
Oh, please.
I'm gonna see your bet...
And raise you 2.
Oh, hush up.
Put your bones in or fold.
Ha ha ha! Roll over and weep!