Oh, my.
Hey, man.
Yo...Dudes.
Huh?
I don't know.
Mm-mmm, look what the hunk
fairy just dropped off.
Jason harrington
and Kyle lawford.
Gloss me.
Sorry. We're watching
the counter for maddie.
We're not allowed to accept money, make
change, or touch any of the merchandise.
Is there anything
you can do?
I can shove 12 gummi worms up my nose.
You wanna see?
Oh, there you are.
Where have you been?
Never mind.
Gloss me, candy girl.
Off the clock.
Thanks, guys.
No problem,
sweet thing.
Aw...
Call me in 10 years.
London?
Kyle.
Hey.
Small world.
Hi. I'm Jason.
Hi. I'm, um...
Uh...
Maddie.
What he said.
So, do you come to
the tipton hotel often?
It's like I live here.
So, Kyle, you in town
for the Usher concert?
Semester break. Our parents
arrive from Aspen tomorrow,
then we fly to Bermuda.
Our moms lost their tans
skiing.
Oh...I hate
when that happens.
Well, as we say, gotta jet.
Nice to meet you.
You don't really
like that guy, do you?
He's cute, but I've worked here
long enough to know his type.
Rich people don't care about
anything but themselves.
Whoa, hey, man,
recycle that.
You serious?
You recycle?
Sure, bottles,
cans, newspapers.
Since when?
Since my father
bought Oregon
and started
chopping down the trees.
You heard of octicorp?
The center of all evil?
That's dad.
I protest against them.
Me, too.
I got dragged off by a cop.
I got grounded for 2 weeks.
I recycle, too.
Really?
I wore these pearls
yesterday.
♪ Here I am in your life ♪
♪ here you are in mine ♪
♪ yes, we have a suite life ♪
♪ most of the time ♪
♪ you and me
got the world to see ♪
♪ so come on down ♪
♪ just me and you
know what to do ♪
♪ so come on down ♪
♪ it's you and me
and me and you ♪
♪ we got the whole place
to ourselves ♪
♪ you and me,
we got it all for free ♪
♪ so come on down ♪
♪ this is the suite life ♪
♪ we've got a suite life ♪
Oh, Kyle, Jason, I got us
tickets to see Usher.
Front row. So close,
he'll probably sweat on us.
Awesome.
Excuse me.
Hey, maddie.
Hi.
What is that all about?
She's all he could
talk about last night.
Oh, please. They are so
not right for each other.
I don't know.
They're both rich.
What? Oh, he thought--
ha! I don't wanna burst
any bubbles,
but it's so much fun.
♪ London, a word ♪
I couldn't help
overhearing your plan.
Oh, good. Then you'll have the
hotel limo ready by 8:00?
Love to, except
your father saw this...
And memoed me,
"no more of these."
But--but--
no "buts."
It is unseemly
that a girl your age
be out alone with 2 boys.
But...
I'm not going alone.
Maddie's coming.
And nobody's gonna have any
real fun with maddie around.
Good point.
Excuse me.
What are you doing?
I'm inviting you to see Usher
with me, Kyle, and Jason.
Why?
Because I'm nice, duh.
Ok. Moseby
won't let me go
unless I bring along a guaranteed killjoy.
So what do you say?
As heartfelt
as that offer is,
no.
Oh, come on. Kyle
says Jason likes you.
Really? Rich guys
don't date poor girls.
Why would Jason
wanna go out with me?
Well, you're smart and cute,
he obviously doesn't mind
girls with big feet,
and he thinks you're rich.
No wonder he's
paying attention to me.
I'll go
set him straight.
No. Just play along.
Please?
It's only for one night.
Front-row seats.
Backstage passes.
You get to ride in a limo
that's not following a hearse.
We get to meet Usher?
Sweetie,
Usher gets to meet us.
Just call me princess.
This whole night
has been so awesome.
Look, I'm a vip.
You know, you're amazing. It's
like this is all new to you--
front-row seats, meeting
celebrities, riding in limos.
Yeah, well,
I never get tired
of sticking my head out of the
sunroof and yelling, "whoo!"
Did you just hear somebody
go, "whoo"?
It must be maddie.
Get down.
I have an idea. Let's
all go to the rooftop,
except for maddie
and Jason.
So, uh, I guess
I should say good-bye.
Or you could invite me
into your suite.
My suite what?
Oh, my suite... in the
hotel where I live
because I'm rich.
No, you can't come in.
I think that creep's
trying to kiss her.
Man, if I was 5 years older
and 2 feet taller.
I'd be squashed.
So you're leaving tomorrow?
Well, I guess we should...
Should
start kissing now.
But I hardly know you.
As a good-bye kiss?
Ok, bye.
Bye.
Both: UNH.
What was that?
Cats.
B-b-big cats.
Actually, they're
the hotel singer's twins.
When she works late,
I let them stay with me.
You are so...
Yes, I am.
Well, I better go.
Uh, not before
you say good-bye.
They're kissing good-bye.
Didn't they just say good-bye?
Hey, thanks for letting me stay the night.
Sure, no problem.
So, word on the street is
that Jason's kind of cute.
Oh, beyond.
And he thinks I'm the most intelligent,
beautiful, down-to-earth rich girl
he's ever met.
Ok, ok, whoa.
Back up. Rich?
It's complicated?
I was doing London
a favor.
It's not like
I wanted to do it.
Oh, yeah, must've been torture
to have to kiss that boy.
Cats told me.
So when are you gonna
tell him the truth?
Never. He's gone.
It was only
for one night,
and I'll never
see him again.
Maddie, can you take us to
the park on your way home?
Sure. Come on.
Don't bring back
another homeless squirrel.
Aw...
[Ring]
Hello?
Oh, no.
Maddie, these are my parents.
Hi, hi.
I, uh, thought you'd be on
your way to Bermuda by now.
Well, so did we. But Jason insisted
on another night in Boston.
And now I know why.
Yeah, Jason has spoken
of nothing but you
all the way from the lobby
up to our room.
And our room is on
a very high floor.
You checking out?
Um, uh...
No. She's moving
to the top floor,
the imperial suite.
Her old suite was the
wrong shade of beige.
Well, we were just coming
down to invite you to dinner.
I convinced them to take us
to club nouveau.
Really? Wow.
I can't go. Yeah, I promised
I'd baby-sit the boys tonight.
Oh, yes, Jason told us about your
charity work with indigent children.
Cody, hey, Josh called.
We're sleeping over
at his house tonight.
Excellent.
Now you can join us.
Uh, uh...
We're on the top floor
as well. In fact,
we'll pick you up.
7:00 sharp.
What am I
going to do?
Here's a wild thought.
Tell 'em the truth.
I don't think so.
I mean,
if I tell them now, Jason will look
like a fool, and I will look like--
a lying gold digger?
Which you're not.
How am I gonna
get out of this?
We'll help you
with Jason.
Why would I help my future wife
hook up with some other dude?
Because he's leaving tomorrow,
and she'll owe you big time.
Ok...Here's what we do--
first, we get you
an imperial suite.
Do you have any idea
how much they cost?
Aw, she thought
we're gonna pay.
That's sweet.
No, we don't pay, baby.
Zack: AND TO GET INTO THE IMPERIAL
SUITE, YOU'LL NEED A KEYCARD.
Whoa.
[Feigns being hurt]
Oh, no. I think
I hurt my coccyx.
[Groans]
All better now, thank you.
Maddie: BUT I DON'T HAVE ANYTHING
TO WEAR TO CLUB NOUVEAU.
Zack: PLEASE.
GIVE US A CHALLENGE.
Hey, Esteban,
moseby's yellin' for ya.
For me? He never
yells for me.
He yells at me, but only when
I deserve it, which is often.
He's a great man.
You're keeping
a great man waiting.
Yeah. But this dress
must go to London.
We'll take it.
Oh, bless you,
little blonde peoples.
Here.
Check it out.
It's a Paris original
from London.
How do I look?
Rich.
[Doorbell rings]
Good.
Enter.
Oh, look. You put the little
inner-city boys to work.
They're so cute.
Be sure you check their
pockets before they leave.
Fabulous view.
You can see the park
from here.
Yes. That's what
trees look like
before you
cut them down.
Ha ha.
Our little rebel.
My son doesn't approve
of what I do
even though it pays
for everything he does.
I know.
Why don't we all
come back up here
after the dinner
that George pays for
and look at the trees
that Jason loves
and have dessert delivered by
that cute Latin waiter I enjoy?
Shouldn't we
be heading out?
I hear club nouveau
is off the hook.
Actually,
all the Boston papers say
that the hottest
ticket in town
is right here
at the hotel tipton.
It's Carey Martin,
the indigent's mother.
She's great. If you only
have one night here,
you've gotta see her.
Although, I'm sure we can
find someone just as good
who is not at this hotel.
Nonsense.
We have reservations.
Heh. So do I.
Keep it movin', folks.
Only the best table
for my friends...
But I don't want
your mom to see us.
Which is way in the back
behind a pole.
Both: WE'RE GOOD.
Alalalalalalal!
Hey, cutie.
Mr. amputator.
Moseby.
A pleasure
to see you again.
Another wrestle royale
at the garden?
The amputator's
here!
He's my favorite
wrestler!
Your imperial suite
awaits.
And he's staying
in maddie's suite.
Is that the expensive one?
Everything at the tipton
is expensive.
Perfect. 'Cause the
promoter's payin' for it.
Oh ho. We'll stick it
to him good.
Yeah!
What do we do now?
We have to get 'em
out of that suite
before maddie
gets back.
Just stall him.
When I'm done with that room,
he's gonna wish
he never checked in.
Need a hand lifting that?
I'm kidding, I'm kidding.
Very good.
Um, m-Mr. amputator, I
don't mean to bother you.
But I'm a big fan. Can
I have your autograph?
Well, of course you can,
young man.
Could you write that
to Cody...
A young man
I have just met?
"Met" is m-e-t.
And yet, I feel
as if I've known him
for a long, long,
long...
Long, long,
long, long...
Oh, is there no end
to this novel?
My apologies.
Don't worry. I put "to Cody--love,
the amputator." How's that?
Yeah, that's cool.
All right.
You know, most celebrities
don't take the time out
to talk
to a kid like me.
Heh.
But
you're different.
So what floor are
you staying on--
5, 12, 14, 17, 20,
basement?
Well, actually,
it's, uh, 25.
But thanks for hittin'
all the buttons for me.
[Ring]
Hello?
Get out now!
I'm warning maddie!
♪ Whisper words
of love and peace ♪
♪ my love,
don't fly away from me ♪
♪ oh, oh... ♪ psst. Maddie!
Shh. Shh. Maddie!
♪ Just when I thought
I'd never see you ♪
♪ here you are
within my reach ♪
♪ you're the truth
I can't ignore ♪
♪ you've become... ♪ does
she always move like that?
No. Normally, she--
na-na-na-na!
Excuse me.
I dropped my fork.
What are you doing here?
Moseby rented your suite
to the amputator!
Really? I love him.
Hello, big picture.
We're getting him out.
I'll call you when
the coast is clear.
Ok.
Are you ok?
Great.
♪ Oh, no, don't run away
from me ♪
♪ mm, hmm, hmm, hmm ♪
Ooh, a quarter.
I have been
looking for you.
Esteban told me
he gave you my Paris original.
Where is it?
Paris?
I'm telling the truth.
Your dress was eaten by
wild Argentinean moths.
Give me my dress
right now!
You told her
we gave it to maddie?
[Gasps]
No.
G-good. 'Cause
we didn't do that.
I'm telling moseby
right now.
N-no. We'll take you to maddie.
You win.
She's changing
in here.
In here? Aah!
Hey! I'm standing
in a bucket!
[Pounding]
Man. Nothin' worse
than wet silk.
Ah.
What else could go wrong?
Ow. Ooh.
Ow. Ow.
All right. Let's put this
puppy back together.
Ok.
You must be
so grateful.
I mean, how many
young girls
would allow a struggling
single mother
with 2 children to
stay in her suite?
It's so much nicer than the
minivan we used to live in.
And wait until you
see her new suite.
I'd love to see
your new suite.
No, you don't wanna
see my new suite.
[Ring]
Yeah?
Ok, let's go see
my new suite.
Ok, they're coming.
We are so good.
Is there a hall of fame
for this kind of stuff?
Yes.
It's called prison.
Both: Mr. MOSEBY.
There's two of them?
Mm, except in my dreams where
I see them by the hundreds.
Oh, boy.
What are all these people
doing in your suite?
Amputator?
[Gasps] I loved your last
steel cage grudge match.
And when your shirt
got torn off--bravo.
Thank you.
No. Thank you.
Maddie,
what's going on?
What's going on is...
Aha! Get out of my dress!
What does she mean,
"her dress?"
She designed it.
Let it go.
She means
it's not mine.
I'm not rich.
I work at the hotel
as a candy counter girl.
I knew she wasn't rich.
She's too nice.
I don't know
what I was thinking.
I was pretending to be
something that I'm not.
I'm sorry.
So do body slams
always hurt?
Wait a second.
Look, I really don't
feel like talking.
Ok. Then I'll talk,
and you listen.
[Crying]
Honey, you really shouldn't have
lied to Jason in the first place.
I know. But I just thought
he wouldn't like me
because we come
from 2 separate worlds.
I mean, he comes from
champagne and caviar
and I come from beer
and pretzels.
[Elevator bell dings]
I'm sorry. Could you please
take the next elevator?
I'm such a doofus,
and now Jason
will hate me.
No. You don't know that.
And you're not giving yourself
very much credit, either.
I know.
I'm such a doofus.
Stop saying that.
Here. May I?
You shouldn't
sell yourself short...
And I bet if you give
Jason half a chance,
he'll tell you
the same thing.
You think so?
I know so.
[Sniffles]
[Blows nose loudly]
Mom, I can't believe
you took away our tv.
Let's review,
shall we?
You destroyed
the imperial suite,
you almost
ruined my show,
you locked London
in a closet,
and you injured a
professional wrestler.
All to help a friend.
And that should be
its own reward.
Mom.
Mom, come on.
Hi.
Uh, um, good morning, sir.
So this is
the real you?
Yep, in all
my blue collar glory.
Listen, Jason,
I'm really sorry
I didn't tell you
the truth.
So am I.
I just thought you were like all
the other rich guys I've met.
You shoulda given me
more credit than that.
I'm sorry.
I wasn't thinking.
So we'll just,
um, say good-bye?
Ok. Good-bye.
Well, you do remember
what we do
when we say good-bye,
right?
I think so.
Again?
How many times
do they have to say good-bye?
Get over it.
I hope you enjoyed
your stay, Mr. amputator.
It was quite relaxing.
Unh! Say your prayers,
amputator!
You're goin' down!
Catch you next week.
The twin terrors have hit
at a fever hold.
Apparently,
not asleep yet.