Love ya.
Hey, Bobby. Thanks.
Thank you.
Great show.
Hey, cute guy.
Third table
from the left.
My left,
not your--hi.
Hi.
Gangway. Coming through.
Watch out.
Zack, what
are you doing?
Winning.
Excuse me. Hi, mom.
Cody!
Stop. Right now.
I hope you don't mind.
I have kids.
Hello?
Cody: LOOK OUT.
Look out!
I can't stop.
Unh.
What is
going on?
If it's not one
thing, it's--
mama!
Aah!
Mr. moseby, are you ok?
Here at the tipton,
it's the guest
that matters,
not the manager.
Look what you guys did.
You broke Mr. moseby.
You are so grounded.
When you say
grounded,
does that include
the pool and gym?
ON THE 23rd FLOOR.
Mr. moseby, I'm sorry.
I won't let them down here
for a long, long time.
Till they go to college.
Or prison.
Oy. Ohh.
Guys, just once would it
kill you to behave?
Both: UHH.
♪ Here I am in your life ♪
♪ here you are in mine ♪
♪ yes, we have a suite life ♪
♪ most of the time ♪
♪ you and me
got the world to see ♪
♪ so come on down ♪
♪ just me and you
know what to do ♪
♪ so come on down ♪
♪ it's you and me
and me and you ♪
♪ we got the whole place
to ourselves ♪
♪ you and me,
we got it all for free ♪
♪ so come on down ♪
♪ this is the suite life ♪
♪ we've got a suite life ♪
Zack: IT'S THERE.
No, it isn't.
Yes, it is.
Right there.
Are you blind?
You can totally feel it.
Ow, you pulled the skin.
That's 'cause
there's no hair there.
And no deodorant.
Aw, you're looking
for armpit hair.
Both: MOM!
My little boys are
becoming little men.
You should really knock.
We don't walk in on you.
Actually, you
do.
And you bring
friends.
Quit it!
Look, we've got to
talk about last night.
We do not want
a repeat
of the dream valley
lodge incident.
I swear I thought
it was a black cat
with a white stripe.
Here's a thought.
What do you say
we keep this job
and get you
a babysitter?
Babysitter?
W-wait, you just said
we were little men.
Ok. A little men sitter.
I was thinking maybe maddie
who works in the gift shop.
She needs the money.
Ooh. Maddie.
Baby's got it
going on.
She's got what
going where?
I don't know
what I'm saying.
Yeah, you better not.
He doesn't.
Yes, I do.
No, you don't.
Mr. moseby.
Good morning.
What a surprise.
Both: GOOD MORNING,
Mr. MOSEBY.
What brings you up
so early?
Couldn't sleep.
Nightmares.
Actually, I am here
to discuss your bill.
What bill?
Room and board
are part of my deal.
Yes, only
you have exceeded
your first month's
allowance by...
[Gasps]
Breathe!
Breathe, mom. Breathe.
[Gasps]
Oh, my.
Mr. moseby,
you can't be serious.
I am powerless
to be otherwise.
I don't know
how this happened.
Man: ROOM SERVICE!
Somebody ordered
the "I'm sorry
for what we did
last night" buffet.
Eggs Benedict
with caviar?
Must be
a mistake.
We ordered toast
and a raisin.
You guys are
bleeding me dry here.
Oh, my mistake.
This was meant
for the other mommy
WITH TWINS
ON THE 23rd FLOOR.
Uh, I'm sorry.
I didn't--I mean
they--they were--
I understand.
Children sometimes
can be a burden.
You have kids?
No, and after seeing
yours, not gonna happen.
Video games,
pay per view--
you had your underwear
dry-cleaned?
Feels good.
Sit.
Now, look, guys.
We may live
in a palace,
but we're
not royalty.
I think
you're a queen, mommy.
Aw.
Put a sock in it.
Come on, guys.
This is the best gig
we've ever had,
and without it,
we're broke.
With it,
Don't you guys
realize
what a great opportunity
this is for us?
I don't have to go out
on the road any more.
We can all
be together.
Yeah, I like it better
here than at grandma's.
Yeah. Last time,
she dropped her false teeth
in my chocolate milk.
I rest my case.
So, please, be good.
Both: WE WILL.
Man: HEY,
NO PHOTOGRAPHERS.
Hey, we live here.
I live here, too.
Hey, check it out.
I found 5 bucks
in my pocket.
Those are my pants.
Cool. Candy's on you. Ok.
Let's hitch a ride.
Shotgun.
Driver,
to the candy shop.
You got it.
Shouldn't we
give the money to mom?
Not until she learns to
manage money better.
We're broke.
Hey, maddie.
I want 2 zabbabbas,
a sweetie tweetie,
and 7-foot
licorice chain.
I see
you're cutting down.
So, guys, I've completely
reorganized the candy display.
Now, tell me,
what draws your eye?
You do, sweet thing.
Please. Some of this candy
is older than you.
Moseby: PAPARAZZI!
I can smell them.
Whoa.
What's
going on here?
They're waiting
for Bobby carillo,
center fielder
for the sox,
and Ursula
the lingerie model.
They're getting married
here on Saturday.
Dude, he's the best player ever.
And she's real good
at what she does.
Oh, yeah. Takes real brains to sit
on a horse in your underwear.
[All talking at once]
I mean, what
is the big deal?
Money, baby.
Tuck.
Hi.
What does he have
that I don't have?
Armpit hair.
Word on the street is the
tabloids are paying $20,000
for a shot of the bride
and groom's first kiss.
You are so plugged in.
This hotel doesn't
run without me.
Are you thinking
what I'm thinking?
Yeah!
What are you thinkin'?
We can take a
picture of the kiss
and we'll be rich.
We can pay mom back.
And we'll be rich.
We won't be burdens
anymore.
And we'll be rich.
And whatever's left,
we can give to charity.
I swear,
we're not related.
Maddie,
I need a camera,
and charge it,
please.
Candy.
Thank you.
Both: WE'RE RICH. WE'RE RICH.
WE'RE RICH.
Not quite.
Nobody is getting
into that wedding
without
a printed invitation.
HERE I AM. LITTLE
ME, BACK FROM  Paris.
Hello, maddie.
Hi, London.
So, how are you getting
into the wedding?
My daddy owns
the hotel. Duh.
Can you
get us in?
Yes, but I'm
not going to. Duh.
I fly solo.
Oh, yeah. Like that time
you let yourself
into that rock star's
room with the master key.
Johnny rip thought
it was endearing.
He even wrote me.
That was
a restraining order.
Look, I'm going
to that wedding.
I'll be on the cover
of this magazine,
and you'll be
selling it. Duh.
We're never
gonna get in here.
There will be security
at every door.
Moseby: AND THIS
IS THE BALLROOM.
This way.
Which we will
magically transform
into your
wedding chapel.
Oh, my.
Where will
beyonc sing
during
the ceremony?
Copenhagen.
Her tour
has been extended.
You know how the danes
like to get down.
♪ Harunky dunky dunky ♪
I am sick of divas.
Can't we just
have a nobody singer
who will
actually show up?
We know
a nobody singer.
It's our mom.
She's a huge nobody.
But I'm sure she's
stretched way too thin
with her show
and policing you.
She could handle it.
Come on.
She's rehearsin' now.
Uh, uh, but--
you'll love her.
She wears
your underwear,
but she looks
a lot different.
♪ To get through it
all ♪
♪ just sing ♪
She's great.
Isn't she great?
Ms. Martin's marvelous.
Everything at the tipton
is marvelous.
Wow, I don't know
how to thank you.
Thank your agents.
Ok. Let's get you
2 lovebirds out of here
without causing a riot,
shall we?
She's perfect.
Ohh.
Whatever you want,
you got it.
Get us
into the wedding.
Except that.
You're grounded,
remember?
You meant that?
I'm doing
the right thing.
Ok. We're just gonna
have to find a way
into that wedding
ourselves.
Forget it.
There is no way
you are talking me
into another one of
your idiotic schemes.
Mad dog to bird dog.
Are you in position?
Affirmative.
I have located
the mezzanine vent.
Hopefully, this one
leads to the ballroom.
It better because
mad dog needs
to find a fire
hydrant and quick.
Roger. I'm sending
down the probe.
You mean
the golf ball?
Yes, the golf ball.
Bingo. We found it,
bird dog.
And what
have we found?
Uh...
My 2-way.
Radio: GET OUT OF THERE BEFORE
LARD BUTT MOSEBY SEES YOU.
Can I just...
Bird dog,
this is lard butt.
You do anything
to disrupt this wedding,
and it will be
the last song
your mother ever sings
at the tipton.
Over and
you're almost out.
No, a dromedary is
not a play about milk.
Ta-da!
Well,
what do you think?
And be brutal.
Anyone looks at you
and they think...25.
And?
And never
had a kid.
Yes! I've trained
them so well.
Ok, now, you gonna
stay in the room
and do everything
maddie says?
Yep.
Good.
Don't believe them.
Ok, guys. Hey.
Double kisses.
Good-bye
and good night.
Carey: LOVE YOU.
Both: LOVE YOU.
Well, I'm gonna
take my bath now.
And I'm going
to brush my teeth
to prevent
dental decay and--
I have one question
about this.
What if we get caught?
Moseby will fire mom.
Who cares?
With 20 grand, we
could buy the hotel
and fire moseby.
Good point.
Now I need
exactly 35 minutes
to get there, get the picture
of the kiss, and get back.
Right. You wanna
synchronize watches?
I don't
have a watch.
Then
we won't do that.
Tv: That's right, Bob.
It's a star-studded event,
the likes of which this
town hasn't seen in years...
Hey, look. You can see the
celebrity guests arriving.
Or you can see it
right here on tv.
Oh, no. I'm falling
out the window.
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow.
Check it out.
A stretch s.U.V. Limo.
Oh, yeah.
Way to waste our planet's
natural resources,
Mr. 6 Miles
per gallon.
Uh-oh.
I think I gotta
go to the bathroom.
Whoa!
[Thud]
Cody. You ok?
I heard
someone fall.
That was Zack.
Right, Zack?
Yes, that was me.
I'm not coordinated
like Cody.
Oh, stop.
Aaaaah!
What are you
doing here?
Checking on my father's
air conditioning vent.
[Bang bang]
Looks good.
Couldn't get in,
huh?
No. [Sighs]
And my best friend
portia tenenbaum is going.
And if I'm not there, she'll
rub it in my face forever.
Now crawl.
Man, it stinks in here.
Sorry.
♪ If ever there was ♪
♪ a heaven on earth ♪
♪ it's here in your arms ♪
♪ you've ended my search ♪
♪ if ever there was ♪
♪ a feeling so right ♪
♪ it must be the way... ♪
It's a longer drop
than I thought.
Don't worry.
I have you.
♪ And after all the... ♪
[Crash]
♪ It's when it's love... ♪
I'm ok.
My head broke the fall.
Zack, Cody. What's
going on in there?
Open this door.
I thought Zack
was taking the bath.
Yeah,
but he splashed me.
Not nice, Zack!
Let me talk to Zack.
Ok. You're
the babysitter.
She wants to talk
to you, Zack.
Ok, Cody.
Here I come, maddie.
Yes.
Can you
make this fast?
There's a draft.
Oh, is that right?
Then I'll
just talk to Cody.
You women
and your moods.
She wants to talk
to you, Cody.
Ok, Zack.
Thank you, Cody.
You're welcome, Zack.
Cody here.
Your sweatshirt's
on backwards.
What's your point?
Whoa!
Where is he?
I'll never
rat him out.
Not in a million
years.
Not in
a billion--
he's in an air
conditioning duct
on the way to the wedding
to get the picture
of the $20,000 kiss.
Grr.
Ow. Ow. Ow. Ow. Ow.
All I wanted to do was
make a little extra money
so I can buy myself
a few nice things
because some of us have
to work for a living
and don't get sent to
Paris as a punishment
for breaking into
Johnny rip's room.
Man, it stinks
in here.
Sorry.
Carey: ♪ OOH, IT'S YOURS ♪
♪ and mine... ♪
Hotel security,
and step on it.
Reverend: TO BE YOUR HUSBAND,
to love and to honor...
Come on, j.Lo.
Move your butt.
By the power vested...
Oh, no.
We're too late.
Yes.
I now pronounce you...
I mean, darn.
You may now kiss the bride.
Hey, that scum's
got a camera.
Camera in the ballroom.
Man: GET HIM! STOP HIM!
Hey. Zack.
Over here.
What is she doing here?
Saving your butt
before I kick it.
Is that a threat
or a promise?
Ugh. Come on.
Stretch.
I can't reach you.
Psst. London.
I need your help.
Give me a boost.
Get down on all fours.
Like, I'm sure.
I wasn't even here.
Take her picture.
Now you were.
When I inherit this hotel,
you're so fired.
Oh, you'll be too busy
getting face lifts.
Maddie: OK, I've ONLY BABYSAT
YOU GUYS FOR 30 MINUTES.
What do you do now,
rob a casino?
We don't
have to.
We hit the
jackpot tonight.
Busted.
[All screaming]
Oh, Carey,
you are great.
Come here.
Oh.
Ms. Martin, I found
these 2 rug rats
in our air
conditioning vent.
What?
Are you crazy?
Exactly. They could
have damaged the vent.
They could have
gotten hurt.
What were you
thinking?
No, I'll tell you what
you were thinking.
You weren't
thinking at all.
That's what you
were thinking.
You were
glorious.
Oh, thank you
very much.
Well?!
We wanted
to hear you sing.
Well, then listen at the door
when I'm
in the shower.
Watch the uniform.
It's rented.
What happened?
Must I be everywhere?
Jerk photographer
crashed the wedding.
Don't move.
I hate those people.
How could he do
something like that?
Maybe he really
needed the money.
Because
he loves his mom.
I don't care
what his reason is.
It's an invasion
of privacy.
Those people are just
low-life, greedy scum.
This is for you.
We didn't sneak in the
vent to hear you sing.
We snuck into the
air conditioning vent
to take
the $20,000 picture.
What?
I am so fired.
We wanted to pay you
back the money.
We wanted to stop
being burdens.
Come here.
I was trying
to stop them.
Better men than you
have tried.
Now, listen.
You're not
burdens, ok?
It's my job to make
the money, not yours.
Your job is to be the
kids and have fun.
And parents take
care of children.
Children don't take
care of parents,
even if they are
becoming little men.
Understand?
Yep. Sorry.
Maybe I did come
on kinda strong
about the whole
being broke thing.
I really shouldn't have
worried you like that.
I was...Wrong.
So, what you're
really saying is
this is all your fault and
we're not really punished?
Nice try.
Yeah, you're grounded
for another week.
When you say grounded--
ON THE 23rd FLOOR.
Race ya upstairs.
Go!
Hey!
Don't run!
Look out!
No!