Mom, please.
Guys, what's wrong
with your old bikes?
They're still
perfectly good.
Mom, they're tricycles.
Guys, I'm sorry, but we can't
afford bikes right now.
I mean, it's that or food.
No, forget I gave
you that option.
Great. Now we're stuck
here with nothing to do.
I mean, this is probably
the most boring hotel
in the history
of boring hotels.
Oh, Zack.
I love this hotel.
♪ Here I am in your life ♪
♪ here you are in mine ♪
♪ yes, we have a suite life ♪
♪ most of the time ♪
♪ you and me
got the world to see ♪
♪ so come on down ♪
♪ just me and you
know what to do ♪
♪ so come on down ♪
♪ it's you and me
and me and you ♪
♪ we got the whole place
to ourselves ♪
♪ you and me,
we got it all for free ♪
♪ so come on down ♪
♪ this is the suite life ♪
♪ we've got a suite life ♪
Wow.
It's like Christmas.
I'm sweating in places
I've never sweated before.
Woman: EXCUSE ME.
Excuse us. Excuse us.
Excuse me.
I need to speak
to the manager--
[bell ringing]
Right away.
Marion moseby
at your service.
Well, Maryann,
my Brianna is
the odds on favorite
to win this years universal
mini-miss beauty pageant.
I've already started
working
on your special
requests.
Hot rollers, high
wattage make up mirror,
and a bucket of fried
possum fingers.
Thank you.
[Car honking]
Oh, excuse me.
My house is double parked.
Remind me to count
the towels in her room.
All right. Moseby booked
a beauty pageant.
I wish we could just
go up and talk to them.
Hello. We can.
Watch and learn,
little brother.
So, if I guess your name,
do I win a kiss?
Aw, you're so
adorable
and so completely
out of your league.
Smooth.
I hate beauty pageants.
I know. I never won
one either.
The point is,
they reward girls
for being shallow,
plastic robots.
What kind of superficial
airhead thinks that's cool?
Isn't this cool?
Oh, that kind.
Look everyone,
it's London.
Miss mini-miss 1999.
[Applause]
BONJOUR  PAGEANT PRETTIES.
Oh, no.
Ohh. What--what are
you doing?
I know that guy.
We were rivals
on the cruise ship circuit.
He's the lowest, most
despicable creep
I've ever known
in my entire life.
Carey!
Tim!
Carey, you look, ugh,
incredible.
What are you doing here?
I work here.
Ah, good for you.
There's no shame
in being a maid.
I'm the, uh, I'm
the host of this pageant.
Actually, I'm
the headliner here.
They've given me a suite
for me and my boys.
Oh, yes. I heard
you had kids.
Don't worry, you'll
get your figure back.
I love your hair.
Did you buy
or lease it?
It was a gift.
So, you like
video games?
There was no
connection.
Ooh. But I think
mini miss Rhode island's
making eyes at me.
None of them have even
noticed me.
Ooh.
[Chimes]
Hi.
[Mumbling]
I'm sorry. I don't
speak vietnamese.
Oh, uh.
I meant, do you need
some help with your bag?
Uh, that's really
nice of you,
but I'm not supposed
to talk to strangers.
Oh, it's ok.
I'm not that strange.
Except for when I get
really nervous,
I can't stop talking.
Which is odd because
I'm aware of it
and you'd think
I'd know better,
but for some
strange reason--
all righty then.
Ok. This thing is
a total washout.
The girls are all
stuck up, phony--
don't talk about her
like that.
She's sweet,
and she's pure,
and everything that's
good about life.
Cody, you just met her.
And yet, I know all I
need to know about her.
Oh, yeah. What's her name?
D'oh!
Not so fast.
Now, these young
ladies are here
for a very important
competition.
Which happens to bring in a
lot of money to this hotel.
They did not come
here to be harassed
by tweedle dumb and
tweedle dumber.
But I have to talk
to what's her name.
Nope, nope, nope.
Nip, nin.
There will be no fraternizing
with the contestants
or I will have your mother
confine you to your hotel suite.
Now, these people are
here as our guests.
We must treat them
like royalty.
Maryann, where can
I dump my porta potty?
If you'll excuse me,
I have to help the
queen with her throne.
How much longer do
we have to wait here?
Until what's
her name comes out
and I can give her
these.
Marion: GOOD DAY.
Oh-uh! Moseby alert.
Oh, no. He's gonna
see us fraternizing.
What are you, 5?
Quick. Hide in here.
Oh, tyreesha, in this dress
you are bound to win.
No, I quit.
I'm sick of beauty pageants.
I'm going to science camp.
Where did I go
wrong?
Tyreesha.
There she is.
What are you doing?
Oh, ladies.
Knock knock.
Man in the house.
Woman: COME ON IN.
We're decent.
Splendid. Splendid.
You know, these rose colored
candies are horrible.
That's soap, madam.
Well, then they're
pretty dang good.
Almost show time, girls.
Come on, come on, come
on, my little beauties.
Come on.
Young lady, why aren't
you in your dress?
Uh.
Number 11.
You're in the first
group.
Ahh, is that a hair
on your lip?
I hope so.
We'll just pull that
right out.
No. Come on.
That's my only one.
Thank you, Tiffany.
Our modeling competition
continues, ladies and gentlemen.
Please welcome
number 11,
miss tyreesha Jones.
[Dance music playing]
Tim: TYREESHA ENJOYS MARINE
BIOLOGY, DOUBLE Dutch,
and her hero is
George Washington...
Carver.
He's out of
his mind.
$2,000!
He's a genius!
Yay, tyreesha!
You go, girl!
Oh, tyreesha,
you were great.
I can't believe I've
never seen you before.
Thanks. I-I-I'm
new to this.
And I'm sure no one
noticed you trip.
And Rebecca, your
dress is so darlin'.
It's just long enough to hide
your scrawny little chicken legs.
Hey, back off or I'll--
I-I-I mean why--why can't we all
just be nice to each other?
You are new.
Thanks for sticking
up for me.
Everyone else has
been kind of mean.
Except for the person who
sent me these pretty flowers.
But they didn't
sign the card.
Uh, it was me.
Me brother Cody.
Arg. I'm a pirate.
Hello...Ladies.
Rebecca, you--you
remember my brother Cody.
Huh?
Cody. You're Cody.
Thanks for the flowers.
Right. Because
I'm Cody,
the one that sent
you the flowers.
Woman: MY DAUGHTER IS TWICE
AS PRETTY AS YOUR DAUGHTER.
Second woman: AAH!
YOU BIT ME.
Ooh, mom's in a cat fight.
I gotta go hold
her earrings.
Look, you were so
hot out there.
You have a chance to
win the prize money.
No way! I'm not doing it.
These heels are killing me
and my panty hose
are riding up.
Who cares about
your female problems?
Think about the money.
Think about the bikes.
You can't drop
out of this pageant.
Forget it.
He's right.
You can't leave.
This pageant is like
a shark tank.
I need you to help
me get through this.
Uh, I'm in.
Hug.
Cody: BOY, EYESHADOW'S
TOUGH TO GET OFF.
'Cause you use
too much.
Which, by the way, makes
you look a little cheap.
Now, I have a great idea for
the talent competition.
[Telephone rings]
Hello.
Oh, hi, Rebecca.
Is tyreesha
there?
Give me that.
Oh, reesha!
Oh, hi, Rebecca.
Sorry to keep you waiting,
but I have to work
overtime to look
as good as you do.
Heh heh heh.
You're so sweet.
Listen, Brianna's having
a slumber party tonight
and asked me
to invite you.
It'd be so much more
fun if you were there.
Wanna come?
A slumber party?
No. Absolutely not.
I'm putting my foot down.
I'll be there.
Clearly you do not understand
the foot down concept.
Hey. This is the only way
I can be with Rebecca
and I'm taking it.
Well, you're gonna
blow your cover
and our chance
to get new bikes.
Tyreesha can do it.
[Imitating girl]
No, tyreesha can't.
Who's tyreesha?
Um, the new weather
girl on tv.
She's always wrong.
40% humidity.
I don't think so.
The tv's not on.
Yeah. That's 'cause
we turned it off.
We're sick of her lies.
Ok.
What do you guys have
planned for tonight?
Um, um, I'm sleeping
over at tapeworm's.
You're not?
Uh, no, we had a fight.
You and
tapeworm?
Me and Zack.
You wearing
lipstick?
That's what the fight
was about.
Uh, I put lipstick on him
while he was taking a nap.
That wasn't very
nice.
And that's not
your shade.
I told you.
[Doorbell rings]
Oh, look, girls,
it's little tyreeta.
Tyreesha.
Like it matters.
Oh, honey, there's
a tray out there
with half a steak
on it.
I'll be right back.
You're just in time.
We're playing what do you
want to be when you grow up.
Ok. Me next.
A supermodel.
Tyreesha, what do
you wanna be?
I'm gonna be
a hockey player.
Uh, or a princess.
Which ever pays
better.
Eh, Rebecca.
I wanna open a free
animal hospital
for underprivileged pets.
I think that's
beautiful.
Thanks. I need to start
saving for vet school now.
That's the only reason
why I'm doing the pageant.
What about you?
Uh, I'm doing it
to buy some bikes.
For underprivileged
pets.
Oh, that's so sweet.
It's so great that
we can do this together.
Hug.
[Doorbell rings]
Be right there.
Don't bother,
darlings.
I own the place.
London.
I got the candy
counter girl
to bring us some
snacks.
Thank you for
introducing me,
but I do have
an actual name.
It's maddie.
London, what did you want
to be when you were little?
I wanted to be
an heiress
and I did it.
Yay, me!
You must be so
proud.
It takes a special
kind of person
to be born rich.
Ahh. Thank you.
What are you doing
in there?
Um, putting
on night creme.
It has to be applied
in the dark.
You know, girls,
pageants have
their place,
but looks aren't
everything.
I mean, there's education
and reading, museums,
becoming a well-rounded person.
Do you know
Orlando bloom?
Of course.
Orlando bloom likes smart girls.
I know he does.
I just know it.
He doesn't.
Girl: OH, NO.
Ow.
So, as returning royalty,
the judge has honored me with
some confidential information
I'm not supposed to tell.
So, here it is.
Is it about
Orlando bloom?
London's talking.
So, after today's events,
it seems the 3 front
runners in the contest are
Brianna--
yes.
No surprise.
Rebecca.
Duh.
And someone named tyreesha.
Brianna, honey,
look.
The maid left the
cart out in the hall.
We are set for
the next 3 months.
Hello, Carey.
Hello, Tim.
Oh, sorry I missed your
little show last night.
I had some socks that
just had to be folded.
I did 3 encores.
That's when you sing more
because they want you to.
Oh, Ms. Martin, how would
you like to do a duet
in the pageant tonight
with Mr. Tim?
When pigs fly.
You fly?
Ms. Martin would be
happy to oblige
such an important guest
who brings so much business
to the tipton hotel.
Apparently it'd
be my pleasure.
♪ She's perfect,
fair and sweet ♪
♪ in a package so petite ♪
♪ what would we do ♪
♪ without her
stunning smile ♪
♪ every lash and curl ♪
♪ of one special
little girl ♪
♪ will prove that
she has gone ♪
♪ the extra mile ♪
♪ only one can be
the best ♪
♪ tough toenails
to the rest ♪
♪ one princess ♪
♪ will bring us total
bliss ♪
Ooh.
♪ She'll be
a universal ♪
♪ mini-miss ♪
Our talent competition continues
with number 17,
Brianna.
[Patriotic music playing]
Ugh. You no good,
stinkin', lousy Baton.
Momma!
Oh, baby.
It's all right.
Brianna.
And Brianna's mom.
Well, it looks like it's
between Rebecca and tyreesha.
Oh, they're so
cute.
I would have
smoked 'em.
I just wanted to say
good luck.
I hope you win
the pageant, tyreesha.
No, you deserve
to win.
You're beautiful,
and unselfish,
and I've never seen anyone
juggle while baking a cake.
You're so sweet.
If you were a boy,
I'd kiss you.
[Sighs]
Dude, those bikes
are ours.
You are so gonna
win this thing.
No, I'm not.
You need to have confidence.
You're such a loser.
What's wrong with you?
I'm throwing
the competition.
Rebecca needs the prize
money for vet school.
We've gone through too much
for you to ruin this now.
We? I'm the one
wearing a dress.
And you've never
looked better.
Well, you better take
a good last look
'cause I'm about
to take it off for good.
I can't believe your gonna let
some girl come between us.
You are not throwing
this competition.
Try and stop me,
pal.
Well, then take off
the dress
'cause I can't hit
a woman.
[Banging]
Cody: Zack, LET ME
OUT OF HERE!
And, now, please
welcome tyreesha Jones
PERFORMING AN Aria
FROM BIZET'S  Carmen.
Oh, I'm sorry here.
There's been
a program change.
Tyreesha will be demonstrating
a brand new talent.
Tyriffic.
[Banging]
Ugh. Where's Zack?
Who?
Tyreesha.
She's out there.
You're ruining Rebecca's
chance at the crown.
You're ruining our
chance for new bikes.
Uh.
Unh.
I don't care about
the bikes.
I care about Rebecca.
Well, I don't.
That's because you only
think of yourself.
[Gasps]
What is going
on?
Nothing out of the ordinary.
Your boys are attempting
to destroy my hotel,
but with a new twist.
One of them's wearing
a dress.
What in the day long
dickens is going on?
I don't know which one
of you is tyreesha,
but she or he is
disqualified.
You're a boy?
Very funny.
You guys are such jerks.
Zack, why are you
wearing a skirt?
I did it so we could
win money for bikes.
Oh, thank goodness.
Hey, man. You ok?
Yeah.
Sorry I ruined it
for you and Rebecca.
I guess I was just being a
selfish, greedy goofball.
Nah, you weren't
greedy.
So we're cool?
We're cool.
I can't believe
I thought a girl
could be more useful
than a bike.
It's ok, buddy.
We all make mistakes.
Well, I'm never making
that mistake again.
From now on, it's
just you and me.
Cody, can I talk
to you?
Buzz off, bike boy.
Hi, Rebecca. Nice tiara.
I'm glad you won.
Thanks to you.
I heard you tried to throw
the competition for me.
I shouldn't have
called you a jerk.
It's ok.
Well, I guess this
is good-bye.
Yeah. Bye.
I hate to say good-bye
'cause, you know,
it's like we just met
and now it's like
you're gonna be leaving
and it's like--
it's ok.
So much better than a bike.
Maryann, I'm just
letting you know
I am not paying
for this movie
'cause I didn't like it.
I'll waive
the fee, madam.
I understand
what it's like
to have to look at something
utterly repulsive.
Thank you.
Uh-huh.