Mom!
Why can't you drive us
to the playground?
Because I have to rehearse
new choreography
for my next show.
Mr. moseby thinks I need
some younger moves.
What do you think?
I think you should
never do that in public.
Or in private.
Why don't you guys
invite over some
friends from school?
That's a great idea.
Too bad
we don't have any.
Nobody ever likes
the new kids.
Come here.
You'll make friends soon.
We're here to stay now.
Not if you use
those moves.
[All gasping]
Impressive catch, Esteban.
If you thought that
was impressive, Mr. moseby,
watch this.
[All yell]
Ooh! I can hear the ocean.
Let me hear!
I wanna hear!
♪ Here I am in your life ♪
♪ here you are in mine ♪
♪ yes, we have a suite life ♪
♪ most of the time ♪
♪ you and me
got the world to see ♪
♪ so come on down ♪
♪ just me and you
know what to do ♪
♪ so come on down ♪
♪ it's you and me
and me and you ♪
♪ we got the whole place
to ourselves ♪
♪ you and me,
we got it all for free ♪
♪ so come on down ♪
♪ this is the suite life ♪
♪ we've got a suite life ♪
London, I need
to speak with you.
Not now, moseby.
I'm off to a gala premier.
Oh, no, you're not.
I just received
a fax from your father.
You are to cease
all social activities
until your grades
improve.
That is so unfair.
I have to keep my grades up,
but his new wife is allowed
to drop out of college?
He also insisted
I hire you a tutor.
When is he gonna realize
that education and me
just don't mix?
Education and I.
Hello? This isn't about you.
Ok. That's $9.12,
minus your 8%
senior discount
is $8.38.
Out of 10?
1.62 is your change.
[Beep]
You beat
the cash register!
And you read!
Maddie can be
your new tutor.
What?!
There isn't enough money
in the world.
I'll pay you
triple your salary.
Apparently there is enough.
Cody, check it out.
It's the drew crew.
Yo, drew.
What up, dawg?
Ha! Hey, look,
it's the clones.
[Crew laughs]
Did you hear that?
The drew crew just
mocked us!
Woo-hoo! We're in.
The drew crew
will never accept you.
Don't beat your head
against a wall.
Even thought
it feels good sometimes.
I'm Max, by the way.
And this is tapeworm.
What kind of name
is that?
The kind you get
when you eat 20 hot dogs
in less than 2 minutes.
Cool!
Beats my record.
By 18.
Hey! You guys wanna
come over to our house?
Did you hear that?
SOMEONE WANTS US
TO COME OVER
TO  THEIR  HOUSE!
♪ Uh uh uh uh uh
uh uh uh ♪
♪ and cross and kick
and step ♪
♪ uh uh and a... ♪
♪ no, no, no,
no, no, no, no ♪
Mom!
O...K.
What are you doing?
Apparently I'm
embarrassing myself
in front of your
new friends.
You made friends!
Maybe.
Whoa!
This is so tight!
I was just rehearsing for--
[hip-hop playing]
My new show.
Man, look at you go.
♪ Hey, hey ♪
♪ dog, slippery dog ♪
♪ dog, eh, dog, eh ♪
Wow!
Can you show me
how you do that?
Sure.
♪ Hey, hey ♪
♪ hey ♪
[Song ends]
Ok. No.
The part a mom
can actually do.
Oh, ok.
So how's your research
on Italy coming?
Oh, fantastic!
I had no idea
fabrizio sold dresses
over the Internet.
I'll order you one.
What are you...
A 14?
Yes!
The same as your iq.
I have to
get downstairs.
He's probably there
already.
Who's there?
No one.
No one who?!
Is he cute?
Ha. It's nothing.
It's just the new lifeguard.
He always buys gum
before his shift.
[Sighs]
Spearmint.
Has he asked you out yet?
Well, not in so many words.
Or in any words really.
I mean, you know how it is
when you really like a guy
and he has no idea
that you exist.
No.
I should go.
I'm late.
You know, if you want
him to notice you,
don't be there.
While he's chewing gum,
he'll be consumed
with thoughts of you.
Where is she?
Why isn't she here?
Is she on a hot date?
Hunh. I never
thought of that.
You may be book smart,
but trust me on this.
When it comes to things
that truly matter,
like dating,
it's time for
the pupil to become
the pupee.
Hey, clones.
Is it true that
you really live
in the tipton hotel?
Yeah, our mom
sings there.
And it makes your place
look like a dump.
Yeah.
And are there really
hot babes serving
ice cream by the pool?
3 flavors.
And we're talkin'
'bout the girls.
Maybe we'll, uh...
Come over and hang out.
You wanna hang out
with us?
Of course, he does.
You know, I've
always liked you 2.
No, you didn't.
Ow! Quit it!
What's up?
So, um...Where
were you yesterday?
'Cause, like,
I was here,
and you weren't.
Oh, I was with--
be mysterious, aloof.
Torture him.
[Pop]
Someone.
Someone...Else.
Really?
Oh, so I guess
that means
you wouldn't want
to go out sometime?
How about tonight?
Whatever you do,
don't look eager.
[Pop]
Not that I'm eager.
I'll check
my calendar.
I'm free.
Excellent.
We'll have dinner
at the seaport.
Hey!
Oh. Hey, London.
Your advice actually worked.
Duh!
What advice?
I got a date with Lance,
the lifeguard.
Oh! So what are you
going to wear?
I don't know.
Jeans?
Why don't you wear
a sack over your head
that says "loser"?
Come on. Let's go
to the boutique.
[Shouting]
Ohh!
Not bad.
Not bad at all.
Check it out, crew.
All this stuff is free.
Free for our guests
who spend $2,000 a day.
Do you have
any hummus?
Ohh. Who ate all
the finger sandwiches?
Who invited ringworm?
It's tapeworm.
Whatever type of worm he is,
please take him
and the rest of your
mongrel horde upstairs
and out of sight.
Come on, guys.
Let's hit the pool!
Please, don't run.
O--ohh!
Just the person
I wanted to talk to.
Ooh. Ooh ooh!
Oh, yeah, that's it.
That's the spot.
Ooh. Thanks, honey.
You were right.
I  WAS  TENSE.
Ooh! 4:00 ice cream.
Like clockwork.
Maybe you guys aren't
so lame after all.
Did you hear that? We're in!
We're not so lame.
We've never been
so popular!
Comin' through.
Ohh! Who ate
all the ice cream?
Too late, earthworm.
Hey, let's all go
in the jacuzzi.
Guys, move over.
Make some room.
Ha! Sorry, but
the kiddie pool's
over there.
Ha ha ha!
Great. First
no finger sandwiches
and then no ice cream
and now this.
They always have extra
in the cabana.
All right!
Better not be melted.
Hey, uh..
Let's ditch the dweebs.
Yep.
Cool.
You guys go ahead.
I'll wait and tell them
where we're going.
Um, he's not clear
on the whole "ditch"
concept.
Look, we just
got past lame.
Don't screw things up.
But mom says we're not
supposed to give in
to peer pressure.
We're not.
We're just doing what
everybody else is doing.
Come on.
But it'll hurt
their feelings.
No, it won't.
They're gonna laugh.
Eventually.
Hi, guys!
Hey.
Where are Max and tapeworm?
Uh...They might not
be here today.
Yo, Zack?
We're out
of finger sandwiches?
Oh.
Whoa, Zack.
Are all these kids
with you?
Yeah, we're part
of their posse.
Guys, I told you
to bring home
a couple of friends,
not the entire school.
Moseby's gonna
blow his top. Fix it.
Ok, mom.
We'll take care of it.
You want to tell drew
not invite any more
of his friends over?
No, it's ok.
You can do it.
WE PROBABLY DON'T HAVE
TO  SAY  ANYTHING.
How many more friends
could he have?
Yo, yo, guys,
over here!
Cool!
Look at this place!
Wow!
Cool!
All right, first one
to the game room
gets free foosball
all afternoon!
[Cheering]
Oh, my--
oh! Oh!
Oh!
Aah!
No! Don't--
[Shouting]
Watch the vase!
Watch the ladd--oh!
Look out
for the vase!
For crying in the--
[shouting]
Everything is fine.
Go have a bite in the bar.
Somebody call my mother!
Call my mother!
Watch the vase!
Don't!
The vase!
Woman: AAH!
I am ok.
I'm fine.
Nothing happened to me.
I am ok. You--
you saved my life.
Oh, Mr. moseby!
Thank you for saving
my life, Mr. moseby.
In my country, my life
now belongs to you.
I want those kids
out of here.
Anyone without
a room key is
on the street.
Well, since my life
now belongs to you,
I must obey
this harsh command.
[Doorbell rings]
So how did it go
with the lifeguard?
Well..
What's the matter?
Didn't he love
your outfit?
Yeah, but...
I don't think
it's going to work.
Why not?
He loved your outfit.
But I didn't like him.
Didn't you like
his outfit?
London, it's not
all about outfits.
It's about the people
inside them.
Huh?
He's really nice, but...
All he can talk about
is water!
Ok? Swimming in water,
diving in water,
splashing water,
salt water versus
fresh water.
After talking to him
for an hour,
I had to go so bad.
[Cell phone rings]
Oh, no, it's him!
Dump him.
Dump him like
last month's shoes.
But I don't want
to hurt him.
Oh, so you're just
going to marry him
and live poolside
with a bunch of boring
lifeguard babies?
[Ring]
You're right.
I got to end it.
Hi, Lance.
Oh, I miss you, too.
Oh, really?
APPARENTLY THE pH BALANCE
IN THE POOL IS PERFECT.
[Doorbell rings]
London, how's
the studying going?
Fabulous.
Thanks for checking in.
Ok. No.
Yes! Yes, I think
chlorine is a...
Beautiful name
for a girl.
Is there any teaching
going on here at all?
Oh, of course.
I'm  TEACHING MADDIE
VALUABLE LIFE SKILLS.
But she is supposed
to be tutoring you.
Your father said
if you flunk out again,
he is sending you
to parochial school.
You mean like
where maddie goes?
I'd have to wear [Gasps]
A uniform?
Mm-hmm.
I can't believe
I made another
date with him.
I can't believe I might
have to wear plaid!
Teach me to be mean.
Teach me to be smart.
Help me!
Good turnout.
All the "a" list kids
are here.
Yeah, but do any of them
even know your name?
Yeah.
Hey, Jack!
Gimme a quarter.
See? Off by one letter.
Psst!
Zack, Cody.
I need to speak
with you.
What's up, Esteban?
I've been given
a terrible task.
I have been ordered
to rid the premises
of children by Mr. moseby.
Now, I could disobey him,
but Mr. moseby reminds me
of my father,
who was also strict,
demanding, ruthless and mean.
Oh, I miss my papa so much.
It's ok.
I need a moment.
We can't ask them
to leave.
They're our friends.
Hey, Zeke! This
stupid machine keeps
stealing all my quarters!
I THINK YOUR  FRIEND
IS TALKING TO YOU, Zeke.
You're right. We got to
get rid of them.
But how?
I know!
Hey! Free foot-long grinders
at the Saint mark hotel
across the street!
[All yelling]
Excellent.
I'll clean out the lobby
and you get the rooftop.
Break!
[Whistling]
Hey.
So for our date,
I was thinking
we'd take a quick swim,
HIT THE JACUZZI,
THEN WATCH  SEABISCUIT.
YOU  DO  KNOW
IT'S ABOUT A HORSE?
A sea horse?
Lance, we need to talk.
See, I think you're
a really great guy and...
Don't beat
around the bush.
The point is...
[Pop]
Life is like an ocean.
It ebbs and flows...
Dump him now!
Don't make me
come out of
this bubble.
Would you be quiet?
[Pop]
Who are you talking to?
No one.
[Sighs]
Look, Lance...
Life is like a river.
Actually I prefer pools.
Ok, that does it.
This isn't working.
I can't go out with someone
who only talks about water.
You're the one that's
talking about water.
Sheesh!
Eee! Good news!
Me, too.
Me first.
I got a d+ in math.
That's good news?
Yeah. Thanks to you,
I passed.
My daddy got me
a plasma tv.
Wow! When I get an a+,
all I get is an extra
slice of pie.
IS THAT  YOUR  GOOD NEWS?
No. No, no.
I took your advice
and broke up with Lance.
I was blunt,
I was direct,
and if I say so myself,
I was pretty darn mean.
So I learned something
from you and you learned
something from me.
Yeah.
And now you have
a plasma tv and...
I don't
have a boyfriend.
So? Everybody's happy.
Eee!
Go, go, go.
Hey, guys,
you need to leave.
Eeyuu! Gross!
Aah!
Don't ask.
How we doing?
I got rid of everybody
downstairs.
Except for one kid
that was crying
and begging to stay.
Turns out his parents
are actually guests here.
Drew.
Drew!
Listen, drew!
Drew, we need
to talk to you.
What?
T-take it away, Zack.
See, the thing is, is
we kinda need you to leave.
We're in the middle
of a game.
No! That
doesn't work for us.
You need to leave.
Tell him why, Zack.
Man, you guys
need to chill,
'cause if we leave,
we're not coming back.
Then you'll have to
hang out with those
2 dweebs Max and silkworm.
His name's tapeworm
and he's our friend!
And so is the other dweeb.
Yeah, and they liked us
even before they knew
we had this cool place
and dainty
finger sandwiches.
That's right! And then
you made us ditch them.
So you know what?
Now we're ditching you.
Give me back the ball.
Fine. Here. Ha!
Ah, Ms. Martin,
I want you to know
I had to use hotel staff
to round up the rabble
your children unleashed
on this hotel.
Mr. moseby, every
little problem with you is like
the sky is falling,
the sky is falling.
[Crash]
Woman: AAH! AAH!
Aah!
Sometimes chicken little
knows what he's
talkin' about.
I can't believe
we broke the hotel.
[Both groaning]
[Grunting]
Ugnh!
Looks like you guys
could use some help.
What are you guys
doing here?
Well, we came here
to tell you off.
But lucky for you,
we overheard you guys
defending us dweebs.
Sorry we ditched ya.
So we're friends
again?
We'll have to
think about it.
Whoa!
[Crash]
Well, could you
think fast?
'Cause I think I
just caught a bus.
Ok.
What have you done?!
Mom!
I am surprised at you 2
and you 2, too!
They didn't do it.
They were the only 2
that stayed to help.
Guys? Hello?
Come on!
It wasn't us.
It was that kid drew.
I told you
he was no good.
You...Said...Nothing!
I don't care
who did it.
Pull!
It's still
your responsibility.
Pull!
When I told you
this hotel is your home,
I meant you should
treat it with respect.
Pull!
Sorry. I guess
I messed up.
That's right.
He messed up.
Pull!
Ooh! 4:00 ice cream.
Guys, guys!
Aw, come on, help!
Oh, man, I picked
the wrong day to wear heels.
You know, moseby,
you run a nice place
around here.
Thanks, son.
I'm a girl.
Mm-hmm.
Cody: THIS IS THE WORST
PUNISHMENT WE EVER GOT!
I think we scrubbed
every single tile.
I can't uncurl my fingers.
Hey, Max! Max, I finally
learned that move.
[Hip-hop playing]
I don't know her.
Neither do I.